

Juan Jose Suarez Romero

Software Developer

How can you contact me?

Cel:

(+57) 301 559 2461

Correo electrónico:

jhanjhuse@gmail.com

LinkedIn

Github

Personal profile

Competent software developer with more than 4 years of experience in both front-end development and back-end development, specialized in problem solving, teamwork, planning and optimization. I have been working with various agile methodologies through different technologies always focused on providing the best results for the company and its customers.

Education

Universidad Cooperativa de Colombia

Computer science

• Aug 2017 - Present

Languages

- Spanish
- English



Employment History

Frontend developer, SunDevs Inc.

Nov 2019 - Present

- Developing front-end with ReactJS using ant design
- Developing front-end with NextJS.

Frontend developer, Gracia's Devs

Mar 2018 - Nov 2019

- Developing responsive websites oriented to multiple screen sizes with bootstrap v4.
- Improving the CSS performance speed over legacy websites intended to optimize their rendering and quality with sass.

Frontend developer, Trinitip

Jul 2017 - Feb 2018

- Developing front-end for a P.O.S. system using Angular +2 v5.
- Developing back-end for a P.O.S. system based in NodeJS with express and MongoDB.

Professional skills

Languages/tools

- Javascript
- HTML
- Css
- Sass
- ReactJs
- Angular +2
- NextJs
- ExpressJs
- Typescript
- Golang



Certifications

Engineering

- Go Hands-on Course: Creating a Web Server Platzi 2021
- Fundamentals Software Engineering Platzi 2021
- Fundamentals Software Arquitecture Platzi 2021
- Course Professional de Git y GitHub Platzi 2021
- Introduction to Terminal and Command Line Course Platzi 2021
- Strategies for an effective e-learning course Platzi 2021
- Basic Go Programming Course Platzi 2021
- MongoDB Basic Course Platzi 2021
- Basic Course in Algorithms and Logical Thinking Platzi 2021
- Curso de Trabajo Remoto o Teletrabajo Platzi 2019

Referencies

Orlando Velasques Diaz

Java Developer at Globant Cel: (+57) 316 802 9772 **Cristhian Gracia**

Full stack developer at SunDevs Cel: (+57) 310 883 4323